Guide to the New York University Archives Photograph Collection PHOTO.00001
New York University Archives
- Washington Square Area
  - Mercer Street (Box 177, Folder 11)
    - Mercer Street - Hot Dog Vendor, 1981; wsa_3_11_07; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 7)
    - Mercer Street and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_3_11_08; Pellettieri, Luigi (Box 177, Folder 11, Item 8)
  - Parsons School of Design/New School (Box 178)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 2 ½ inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 1)
    - Parsons School of Design, circa 1960s-1970s; wsa_3_12_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 x 4 inches (Box 177, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - New Sailors' Snug Harbor Properties, 1947-1955 (Box 178)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, 1947; wsa_3_13_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 1)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - South side, looking east, 1948; wsa_3_13_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 2)
    - Washington Mews No. 12, 1948; wsa_3_13_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Folder 3)
    - Washington Mews, No. 12, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 4)
    - Washington Mews No. 12 - south side, looking east, circa 1947; wsa_3_13_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 5)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, circa 1946; wsa_3_13_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 6)
    - 262 Sailors Snug Harbor, circa 1940s-1950s; wsa_3_13_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 7)
    - South Side of Washington Mews, Looking East, 1955; wsa_3_13_08; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 177, Folder 13, Item 8)
  - Provincetown Playhouse, 1936 (Box 178)
    - Provincetown Playhouse, 133 MacDougal Street, 1936; wsa_3_14_01; Abbott, Berenice, 1898-1991; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178)
  - 6th Avenue, 1940s, 1940-1949 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Looking North at East Side of Sixth Avenue, From Washington Place Towards Waverly Place., Circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 1)
    - 6th Avenue "El" Turning West Into West 3rd and West Broadway, circa 1940-1949; wsa_3_15_02; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 2)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_03; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 3)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, From Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_04; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 4)
    - Looking East from 6th Avenue at the North Side of Waverly Place, 1945; wsa_3_15_05; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 5)
    - West Side of 6th Avenue Between 3rd and 4th Streets, 1945; wsa_3_15_06; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 6)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, from West 4th Street, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_07; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 7)
    - West Side of MacDougal Street, looking South from Intersection of Washington Square South and Washington Square West, 1945; wsa_3_15_08; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 8)
    - Looking South at East Side of 6th Avenue, from Washington Place, circa 1947; wsa_3_15_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 9)
    - Looking North at East Side of 6th Avenue, towards 8th Street, 1945; wsa_3_15_10; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 15, Item 10)
    - 6th Avenue, 1860; cuid17562 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - 6th Avenue, 6th and 14th, cuid17563 (Box 178, Folder 16)
  - Slum Clearance Project (Between West 3rd and Houston), 1950-1959 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - 6th Avenue El turning west onto West 3rd Street, wsa_3_17_01; Roberto, Joseph J.; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 4 3/4 x 6 5/8 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 1)
    - Site of Loeb Student Center, demolition of old building, Washington Square South, November 12, 1957; wsa_3_17_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 2)
    - Demolition, Washington Square South, June 19, 1957; wsa_3_17_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 3)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, West Houston between Wooster and West Broadway (north side)., 1955; wsa_3_17_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 7, Item 4)
    - Washington Square Project, Southeast Slum Area, North side of West 3rd Street between Wooster and W. Broadway., 1955; wsa_3_17_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 17, Item 5)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue's Cemetery (West 11th Street), 1970 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 1)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 2)
    - Spanish and Portuguese Synagogue Cemetery, West 11th Street, September 16, 1970; wsa_3_18_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 18, Item 3)
  - Studio Building (51 West 10th), 1858 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Studio Building, 51 West 10th Street, 1858; wsa_3_19_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 178, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Fires, NYU and area (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Fire Alarm at Rubin Residence Hall (exterior), 1981; wsa_3_1_01; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Firemen, undated; wsa_3_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Westside Pier, undated; wsa_3_1_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - Firefighter at Work in Silhouette, undated; wsa_3_1_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - Fire at Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_3_1_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_06; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 6)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_07; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 7)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Waverly, 1984; wsa_3_1_08; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 8)
    - Aftermath of Fire in Main Building, 1983; wsa_3_1_09; Chait, Marc W.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_10; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 10)
    - Joseph G. Fitzgerald, Assistant Director and Manager Protection Department, 1981; wsa_3_1_11; Friedman, Mark; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 11)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books, undated; wsa_3_1_12; black-and-white print (photograph), 2 x 3 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 12)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_13; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - Silhouette of Fireman, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_14; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 14)
    - Firefighters, Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_15; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 15)
    - Fireman, undated; wsa_3_1_16; Shiotani, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 16)
    - Fire on Sullivan Street, 1983; wsa_3_1_17; Charry, Jonathan; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 17)
    - Fire, Sixth Avenue, 1981; wsa_3_1_18; Comer, Philippe; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 18)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_19; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 19)
    - Firefighters, undated; wsa_3_1_20; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 20)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_21; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 21)
    - Firefighters at Westside Piers, undated; wsa_3_1_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 22)
    - Fire, Bleecker Street, undated; wsa_3_1_23 (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 23)
    - Aftermath of Fire at Wilentz's Books (exterior), undated; wsa_3_1_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 1, Item 24)
  - Grace Church (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Grace Church (engraving), undated; wsa_3_2_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Subway Stations (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Subway Station (West 4th Street), 1980; wsa_4_1_01; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 1)
    - TSOA Students at West 4th Street Subways, 1988; wsa_4_1_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 2)
      Student activities.; Greenwich Village (New York, N.Y.)
    - 7th Avenue Subway Station, wsa_4_1_03; Occhiogrosso, Paul; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 3)
    - Subway Entrance 6th Avenue and West 3rd Street, circa 1950-1959; wsa_4_1_04; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 4)
    - 8th Street Subway Station, 1973; wsa_4_1_05; New York University; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Sullivan Street (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Sullivan Street and Washington Square South, Aerial View, wsa_4_2_01; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 ½x 4 ½ inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 1)
    - Googie's Bar, 1981; wsa_4_2_02; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 2)
    - Googie's Bar, 1981; wsa_4_2_03; Katz, Ken; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 3)
    - Sullivan Street and Washington Square South, wsa_4_2_04; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 8 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 4)
    - Newsstand, wsa_4_2_05; Gurian, Mal; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 1/4 x 9 3/4 inches (Box 179, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Thompson Street (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Washington Square South and Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_01; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 6 1/2 x 4 3/4 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 1)
    - Looking South at East Side of Thompson Street, from Washington Square South, wsa_4_3_02; Mantel, Muriel; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 2)
    - Pinto's on Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 3)
    - Looking North along Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_04; Cole, Roberto, 1915-1983; black-and-white print (photograph), 7 3/4 x 7 1/2 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 4)
    - Arch Cafe on Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 5)
    - Ernie's, 1959; wsa_4_3_06; Simmons, William; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 6)
    - Oasis at Washington Square South and Thompson Street, wsa_4_3_07; Beals, Jessie Tarbox; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 7)
    - Thompson Street and West Broadway, wsa_4_3_08; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - Looking North at the East Side of Thompson Street, circa 1948; wsa_4_3_09; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - Trinity Trade School (35 Washington Square West), 1942 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Trinity Trade School, no. 35 Washington Square West, undated; wsa_4_4_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 6, Item 1)
    - Trinity School, Wall Street Divisions, 1942; wsa_4_4_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Twain, Mark - Residence of (14 West 10th Street), 1970 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Mark Twain House, 14 West 10th Street, 1970; wsa_4_5_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Unidentified photos of Washington Square Area (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Law Center, Washington Square South, 1965; wsa_4_6_01; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 1)
    - Waverly Building (door), 1965; wsa_4_6_02; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 2)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_03; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 3)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_04; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_05; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 5)
    - no. 48-50 West 4th Street, 1965; wsa_4_6_06; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 6)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_07; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 7)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_08; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 8)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_09; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 9)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_10; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 10)
    - Brown Building, 1965; wsa_4_6_11; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_12; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_13; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 13)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_14; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 12)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_15; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 15)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_16; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 16)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_17; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 17)
    - Rooftops, Washington Square Area, undated; wsa_4_6_18; Sozio, A.F.; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 18)
    - View from Rooftop of Intersection, Washington Square Area, 1965; wsa_4_6_19; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 19)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_20; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 20)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_21; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 21)
    - "4" - Address Number, 1976; wsa_4_6_22; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 22)
    - "239" - Address Sign, 1976; wsa_4_6_23; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 23)
    - "50" and Torch Logo, Address Sign, 1976; wsa_4_6_24; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 24)
    - 33 Washington Square West, 1965; wsa_4_6_25; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 25)
    - Division of General Education, 1965; wsa_4_6_26; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 26)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_27; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 27)
    - Washington Square Area, 1965; wsa_4_6_28; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 28)
    - Campus Building and Pile of Pipes, 1965; wsa_4_6_29; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 29)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_30; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 30)
    - Washington Square Area, circa 1930 - 1950; wsa_4_6_31; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 31)
    - Washington Square Area, 1964; wsa_4_6_32; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 32)
    - Townhouse on Fire, undated; wsa_4_6_33; Kralwich, Sara; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 33)
    - Building (drawing), 1963; wsa_4_6_34; black-and-white drawing (ink), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 34)
    - Building, Washington Square Area, undated; wsa_4_6_35; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 35)
    - Buildings, Southwest Corner of Washington Square Park, circa 1950 - 1959; wsa_4_6_36; Mal Gurian Associates; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 36)
    - Buildings, Washington Square Area, 1964; wsa_4_6_37; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 37)
    - Street, Washington Square Area, Shot from Rooftop, 1965; wsa_4_6_38; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 38)
    - Street, Washington Square Area, 1964; wsa_4_6_39; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 39)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_6_40; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 40)
    - View from Rooftop of Intersection, Washington Square Area, 1965; wsa_4_6_41; Seligson, Stanley; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 41)
    - Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_42; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 42)
    - Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_43; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 43)
    - Mayfair Smith Apartments, circa 1965 - 1975; wsa_4_6_44; black-and-white print (photograph), 11 x 14 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 44)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Area, undated; wsa_4_6_45; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 45)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Area, undated; wsa_4_6_46; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 46)
    - Remodeling Interior of Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_47; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 47)
    - Remodeling Interior of Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_48; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 48)
    - Remodeling Exterior of Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_49; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 49)
    - Remodeling Exterior of Unidentified Building, undated; wsa_4_6_50; color print (photograph), 3 x 5 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 50)
    - Street Corner and Scaffolding, 1949; wsa_4_6_51; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 179, Folder 8, Item 51)
  - University Place (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Building, Washington Square Campus, 1965; wsa_4_7_01; black-and-white print (Polaroid (TM) transfer print), 3 x 5 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - South Side of East 8th Street Looking East from Fifth Avenue, undated; wsa_4_7_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - East Side of University Place Looking South from East 8th Street, undated; wsa_4_7_03; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 3)
    - no. 1 University Place at Waverly Place, undated; wsa_4_7_04; Sihler, Henry J.; black-and-white print (photograph), 5 x 7 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 4)
    - University Place at Waverly, circa 1925 - 1935; wsa_4_7_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 5)
    - Rooftops, Looking Northwest from Roof of Main Building, 1949; wsa_4_7_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Waverly Place (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - 25 Waverly Place, 1969; wsa_5_1_01; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 181, Folder 1, Item 1)
    - Waverly, 1964; wsa_5_1_02; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 181, Folder 1, Item 2)
    - Northern Dispensary Building, undated; wsa_5_1_03; black-and-white print (laserjet), 8 x 10 inches (Box 181, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Washington Place (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - South Side of Waverly Place Looking East from Sixth Avenue, 1945; wsa_4_8_01; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 1)
    - Third Street and Thompson Street, 1959; wsa_4_8_02; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 2)
    - Washington Square East and Washington Place, 1964; wsa_4_8_03 (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 3)
    - Washington Place, 1964; wsa_4_8_04; Pellettieri, Luigi; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - East Side of Sixth Avenue Looking North from Washington Place, 1945; wsa_4_8_05; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 5)
    - Washington Square and Waverly Place, 1945; wsa_4_8_06; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 6)
    - Washington Place East, Including Former Residence of Henry James Sr., 1892; wsa_4_8_07; black-and-white print (photograph), 8 x 10 inches (Box 180, Folder 2, Item 7)